Now in this lecture, we're going to do a quick hands-on
on Amazon bedrock guardrails.
So I'm already on the Amazon bedrock service.
So let me just scroll down and here I can see guardrails.
Let me just click on this guardrails.
And then I can just click on this create guardrails.
Now let's just assume that you are an investment banking firm
and you have built a chatbot that leverages a foundation model.
And it helps answer customer queries
related to their portfolio.
So you want to set up bedrock guardrails
so that your chatbot is compliant
with the organization responsible AI policies.
And additionally, you want to make sure
that your chatbot does not answer any questions related
to investment advice.
OK, now let's go ahead and give the name to this guardrails.
So let me just say investment advice
and then you can give description.
If you want, then we have message for block prompts.
So for any reason, if your bedrock guardrails blocks
a particular prompt from your customer,
what is a message that he should get?
So you can define the message here, the default message is sorry,
the model cannot answer this question.
Then you can also enable cross region influencing
if you want.
So let me just enable this.
So what this does is basically if there is not enough capacity
in the region you're operating, then it
can send your request to a different region.
OK, then we have KMS, if you want encrypt your data,
then you have tags is optional.
So I'm going to skip that.
Let me just click on next.
So the first thing you have is configure content filters.
So content filters can detect and filter harmful inputs
and model response.
So if you see a harmful category, so if I just configure this.
So then you can see the harmful categories here.
So you have hate, insult, sexual, violence, and misconduct.
And then you can have guard action.
You can either block or just detect.
And then you can also set the threshold.
So if you set high threshold, then anything
that remotely looks like hate is going to be blocked.
If you say set low on none, then it's
going to enable a lot of those queries.
Next, we have the prompt attack.
So enable to detect and block user prompts,
attempting to override the system instructions.
So if there is such end user inputs or prompts
that try to override the instructions
that you have given to the large language model,
then those can be blocked.
So if I just click on this.
So here you see prompt attacks.
And it says describe user prompts intended
to bypass the CFT and moderation
capabilities of the foundation model.
So we already discussed that most foundation models already
have some sort of safeguards built in.
But if there is a user prompt is written in such a way
that it tries to bypass that CFT and moderation
capabilities of foundation model that's called as a prompt attack.
You can block the prompt attack through text or image.
And then again, you define the action
and you set the threshold.
And then you also have the content filter tiers.
So you have the classic, which is the older one
and establish solution supporting English, French,
and Spanish, and in this tier, you don't need to offer cross-region
inference.
And then you have the standard, which
is the more improved robust solution, offering higher accuracy,
supports 50 languages.
And you have to opt into cross-region inference
if you want to use this.
So let me just select classic.
And then let me just click on next.
The next we have the denied topics.
So you can add up to 30 denied topics.
So in our case, we said we're going to block any topic.
That is related to investment advice.
So let me just click on add denied topic.
And let me just say the same thing, investment advice.
So let me just say, block anything related
to investment advice topic.
And in production amount, obviously, you
will write more details.
But for now, we're just going to keep it simple.
And then you have to define the input and output action.
So if there is a question related to investment advice,
choose what action the guardrails should take on user input
before they reach the model.
So maybe we'll just say block even before it goes to the model.
And then similarly, you can define the output.
So let's say if something related to investment advice
is generated by the foundation model,
should it go to the user or not?
Block it both at input and output.
So let me just say confirm.
Then let me just click on next.
And here you have add word filters.
Use these filters to block certain words and phrases
in your user input and model response.
So if you want to block any particular words,
you can define those words here.
So you can define up to 10,000 words.
So you can just here click on add, add word or phrase.
And then you can just write the word.
So let me just say violence.
And then I can just do a tick here.
And then I can just say block.
So that's how you can define any words that you want to block.
So now let me just click on next.
Add sensitive information filters.
Use these filters to handle any data related to privacy.
So if you want to filter any PI data,
then you can do this here.
So you can see here we have add new PI.
And if I just click on this, add all PI at type.
So these are all the PI types that you can add.
Maybe you can add name, phone, and then you
can define the input and output action.
So let me just click on next.
Next, we have the contextual grounding check.
So this is mainly used to reduce the hallucination
of the foundation model or the large language model.
So previously we had discussed the chatbot
for the investment bank that answers the user queries.
Let's say the end user asks a question
on what are the top 50 stocks in the Indian stock market.
And bank has provided PDF as a data source,
which is answered to these questions.
So what bedrock guardrails contextual grounding check
is going to do is it's going to validate the answer generated
by the foundation model with that particular PDF
and come up with a confidence score.
Now if I just go to this grounding and enable grounding check,
you can see what you have to do is you have to define
the grounding score threshold.
Now let's say you define the grounding score threshold
as 0.74.
So the confidence score that was generated
by this bedrock guardrails grounding is more than 0.74.
Then it's going to respond.
But if it's less than 0.074, it's going to either block
or detect that answer based on your selection
from the drop top.
And the relevance validates the response generated
by the foundation model or the large language model.
If it is relevant in the context of the question posed
by the user.
So let's say user asks again the same question
top 50 stocks in Indian stock market
and the foundation model generates a response
highlighting the top 50 stocks in the US market.
So this is not relevant response to the user query.
Even though the source data might have details related
to the top 50 stocks in the US market.
So when you enable this relevance check
and define the threshold score, what bedrock guardrails
is going to do is it's going to come up with the confidence
score based on the user query, the model response
and what's there in the document source.
And then based on the threshold response,
if it is below the threshold response,
then it's going to block.
If it's more than the threshold response,
then it's going to generate a response.
Okay, and then we have the automated reasoning check.
So this is another capability provided as part
of the bedrock guardrails, which helps reduce model
hallucination.
Now if I just click on this enable automated reasoning,
one thing I want to highlight here is automated reasoning,
checks operating detect mode only.
So it works in detect mode only.
This means it will provide feedback
for all the relevant content but won't block response
from your element.
So till now for all the other capability we saw,
we had two options to detect and block.
But in case of automated reasoning,
it only does detect.
Okay, then again you select the confidence threshold
and what additionally you need to do is,
you need to attach some policies.
You can configure up to two automated reasoning policies
per guardrails.
So basically what you do in automated reasoning,
you create a policy document.
And then this automated reasoning extract all the business
rules from that policy document.
So before the response generated by the foundation model
is sent to the end user, the bedrock guardrails
would do an automated reasoning check.
So we're going to deep dive into automated reasoning check
in the next few lectures.
Okay, so let me just disable this
and let me just click on next.
So now we can go ahead and review the guardrails
and let me just click on this create guardrails.
So I've waited a few minutes
and I have this guardrails investment advice
and status as ready.
Now what I can do is I can just select a model here.
Let me just select this Amazon no more pro apply.
Now here I can just type a prompt.
So we had enabled the content filter.
So let me type a malicious prompt.
So let me just say how to kill someone.
And now if I just do a run,
so you can see here guardrails action,
intervened one instance.
And the response is generally sorry,
the model cannot answer this question.
If I just click on view trace.
And here in the content filter that we had.
So under violence, you can see it's blocked
and it's showing us confidence high.
Now let me just go ahead and ask another question
and let me just say give me investment advice.
Remember we had blocked this particular topic
and let me just scroll down and let me just say run.
And now here you can see again,
it's showing intervened one instance.
Sorry the model cannot answer this question.
And if I just go here investment advice blocked.
So it's blocking this because investment advice
was a denied topic.
Now if I just go back to my guardrails.
So now here you can see investment advice
and this is my ID and this is my name.
Now if you're just thinking how do we actually use it
programmatically in our JNA application?
So you can see we have the name here,
we have the ID and we have the AR.
So if I just go back to the slides.
So this is my request syntax in motor three.
So this is a particular method called as invoke model.
So here I send the body and there's some model ID
and some other parameters.
But here you can see you can provide the guardrail identifier,
the string and then you can also provide the version.
So once you provide those two details,
then it should automatically block the configuration
that you have set in the bedrock guardrails.
Okay, so that's pretty much it from this lecture.
I'll see in the next lecture.